Guide to the Yale Diploma Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Diploma Collection
1702-1950
RU 150
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
29.2
The collection consists of diplomas awarded by Yale.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 47 (YRG 47), Collections documenting teaching and learning in Yale academic programs.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of diplomas awarded by Yale.
Diplomas; Yale College (1718-1887) -- Students; Yale University -- Students
- Inventory, Accession 19ND-A-400
  - Nathaniel Chauncy, MA [original and copies], 1702 (Box 1)
  - Stephen Buckingham, MA, 1702 (Box 1)
  - John Hart, BA [original and photostat], 1703 (Box 1)
  - Samuel Whittelsley, MA, 1707 (Box 1)
  - Daniel Boardman, BA, 1709 (Box 1)
  - Daniel Boardman, MA [original and photostat], 1712 (Box 1)
  - Benjamin Lord, BA, 1714 (Box 1)
  - James Pierpont, BA, 1718 (Box 1)
  - Benjamin Lord, MA, 1719 (Box 1)
  - Samuel Mix, BA, 1720 (Box 1)
  - John Beach, BA, 1721 (Box 1)
  - James Pierpont, MA, 1721 (Box 1)
  - Josiah Frisbie, BA [original and photostats], 1722 (Box 1)
  - Jeremiah Curtis, BA [original and photostats], 1724 (Box 1)
  - Isaac Stiles, MA, 1725 (Box 1)
  - John Whiting, BA, 1726 (Box 1)
  - Jeremiah Curtis, MA [copy?], 1727 (Box 1)
  - Theophilus Hall, BA, 1727 (Box 1)
  - George Beckwith, BA [original and transcription], 1728 (Box 1)
  - Jonathan Ashley, MA [photostat, original on loan to J.A. House, Deerfield], 1733 (Box 1)
  - Daniel Gardiner, BA, 1736 (Box 1)
  - Daniel Lathrop, MA, 1736 (Box 1)
  - William Nicoll, MA, 1737 (Box 1)
  - Ephraim Strong, BA, 1737 (Box 1)
  - Stephen Wakeman, BA, 1738 (Box 1)
  - Benjamin Woodbridge, BA, 1740 (Box 1)
  - Thomas Balch, MA [honorary], 1741 (Box 1)
  - Noah Wells, BA [original and photostat], 1741 (Box 1)
  - Noah Wells, MA, 1744 (Box 1)
  - Daniel Brinsmade, BA [photostats], 1745 (Box 1)
  - Izrahiah Wetmore, BA, 1748 (Box 1)
  - Judah Clapham, BA [photostat], 1751 (Box 1)
  - Izrahiah Wetmore, MA, 1751 (Box 1)
  - Elizur Goodrich, BA, 1752 (Box 1)
  - Stephen Holmes, BA, 1752 (Box 1)
  - Benjamin Franklin, MA [honorary - photostat], 1753 (Box 1)
  - William Williams, MA, 1753 (Box 1)
  - Richard Ely, BA, 1754 (Box 1)
  - William R. Miner, BA, 1756 (Box 1)
  - Sylvanus Griswold, BA, 1757 (Box 1)
  - Ezra Reeve, BA, 1757 (Box 1)
  - Noah Williston, BA, 1757 (Box 1)
  - Jonathan Ashley, BA, 1758 (Box 1)
  - Thomas Burgiss, BA, 1758 (Box 1)
  - Ambrose Collins, BA, 1758 (Box 1)
  - Thomas Niles, BA, 1758 (Box 1)
  - F. (?) Gay, BA, 1759 (Box 2)
  - Nathaniel Hubbard, BA, 1759 (Box 2)
  - John Smalley, MA, 1759 (Box 2)
  - Benjamin Trumbull, 1759 (Box 2)
  - Isaac Jones, MA, 1760 (Box 2)
  - William Lynde, BA [photocopy], 1760 (Box 2)
  - Charles Smith, MA, 1760 (Box 2)
  - Philip Dagget(t), BA [original and photocopies], 1762 (Box 2)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Original diploma: Gift of Kathleen P. Eden, Executor of the Estate of Bronson B. T. Eden, 2017.
  - Consider Morgan, BA [original and photostat]
  - Robert Geer, BA [original and photostat], 1763 (Box 2)
  - Stephen Mitchell, BA, 1763 (Box 2)
  - Diodate Johnson, BA, 1764 (Box 2)
  - Elisha Baker, MA, 1765 (Box 2)
  - John Foot, BA, 1765 (Box 2)
  - Elam Potter, BA, 1765 (Box 2)
  - Jonathan Ingersoll, BA, 1766 (Box 2)
  - Samuel Huntting, BA [photocopy only], 1767 (Box 2)
  - Jonathan Bird, BA, 1768 (Box 2)
  - John Ford, BA, 1768 (Box 2)
  - Robert Walker, MA, 1768 (Box 2)
  - Charles Backus, BA [original and 4 copies]
  - Daniel Grosvenor, BA [3 copies only], 1769 (Box 2)
  - Jonathan Ingersoll, MA, 1769 (Box 3)
  - John Lewis, BA, 1770 (Box 4)
  - Henry Daggett, BA, 1771 (Box 4)
  - Allen Mather, BA [original and 2 copies], 1771 (Box 4)
  - Thomas Canfield, BA, 1772 (Box 4)
  - Bela Elderkin, BA [unsigned], 1772 (Box 4)
  - James Hillhouse, BA, 1773 (Box 4)
  - Elihu Marvin, BA, 1773 (Box 4)
  - Peabody Clement, BA, 1774 (Box 4)
  - Benjamin Lord, DD, 1774 (Box 4)
  - Thomas Welles, BA, 1774 (Box 4)
  - Naphthali Daggett, DD [hon] from Princeton - photocopy, 1774 (Box 4)
  - Stephen Bradley, BA, 1775 (Box 4)
  - James Briggs, BA, 1775 (Box 4)
  - Daniel Brinsmade, MA [3 photocopies], 1775 (Box 4)
  - Jabez Colton, BA, 1775 (Box 4)
  - Henry Daggett, BA, 1775 (Box 4)
  - Joshua Johnson, BA, 1775 (Box 4)
  - Adoniram Judson, BA, 1775 (Box 4)
  - Solomon Porter, BA, 1775 (Box 4)
  - Nehemiah Prudden, BA, 1775 (Box 4)
  - Richard Sill, BA, 1775 (Box 4)
  - James Hillhouse, MA, 1776 (Box 4)
  - Samuel Mills, BA, 1776 (Box 4)
  - Martin Phelps, BA, 1775 (Box 4)
  - William Frederic Hotchkiss, BA [photocopy only], 1778 (Box 4)
  - John Morgan, MA, 1778 (Box 4)
  - Adoniram Judson, MA, 1778 (Box 4)
  - Nehemiah Prudden, MA, 1778 (Box 4)
  - Asa Spalding, BA, 1778 (Box 4)
  - Charles Chauncey, MA [honorary], 1779 (Box 4)
  - Roderic Lawrence, MA, 1779 (Box 4)
  - John Barker, MA, 1780 (Box 4)
  - Stephen Chester, BA, 1780 (Box 4)
  - Eli Curtis, MA, 1780 (Box 4)
  - Samuel Nott, BA, 1780 (Box 4)
  - Daniel Potter, BA, 1780 (Box 4)
  - Jonathan Nicoll Havens, MA, 1781 (Box 5)
  - Samuel Mills, MA, 1781 (Box 5)
  - Israel Smith, BA, 1781 (Box 5)
  - T. Lucius Wooster, BA, 1781 (Box 5)
  - Elizur Wight, BA, 1781 (Box 5)
  - Elizur Goodrich, MA, 1782 (Box 5)
  - Matthew Russell, MA [photocopy], 1782 (Box 5)
  - Samuel Woodruff, BA, 1782 (Box 5)
  - David Wright, MA [photocopy], 1782 (Box 5)
  - Jonathan Merick, BA, 1783 (Box 5)
  - Jedediah Morse, BA, 1783 (Box 5)
  - Samuel Nott, MA, 1783 (Box 5)
  - Noah A. Phelps, BA [damaged], 1783 (Box 5)
  - William Brown, BA [original and photostat], 1874 (Box 5)
  - Ralph Isaacs, BA, 1784 (Box 5)
  - Jared Spencer, BA, 1784 (Box 5)
  - Joseph Strong, BA, 1784 (Box 5)
  - Thomas Goodsell Woolcott, BA, 1784 (Box 5)
  - Jonathan Leavitt, BA, 1785 (Box 5)
  - Zachary Olmstead, BA, 1785
    General note
    [note on Elias Perkins Diploma - Transferred to E.P. Papers, Mss Group 1013]
  - John Witherspoon, 1785 LL.D. [honorary] (Box 5)
  - George Selden, BA, 1786 (Box 5)
  - Isaac Stiles, MA, 1786 (Box 5)
  - John Bishop, BA, 1787 (Box 5)
  - Joseph Foot, BA, 1787 (Box 5)
  - Elisam Leonard Lathrup, BA, 1787 (Box 5)
  - Richard Morris, MA. [honorary], 1787 (Box 5)
  - Adna Stanley, BA, 1787 (Box 5)
  - Elisha Sterling, BA, 1787 (Box 5)
  - Eli Todd, BA, 1787 (Box 5)
  - Jonathan Leavitt, MA., 1788 (Box 5)
  - Jonathan W. Edwards, BA, 1789 (Box 5)
  - Daniel Lathrop, BA, 1789 (Box 5)
  - William Leffingwell, MA, 1789 (Box 5)
  - Samuel Lockwood, DD [draft? early copy?]
  - Elias Boudinot, J.D. [honorary? original and photocopy], 1790 (Box 5)
  - Lyman Law, BA, 1791 (Box 5)
  - Daniel Smith, BA, 1791 (Box 5)
  - Josiah Stebbins, BA, 1791 (Box 5)
  - William Botsford, BA (copies), 1792 (Box 5)
  - Jonathan W. Edwards, MA, 1792 (Box 5)
  - Donald Grant Mitchell, BA, 1792 (Box 5)
  - Asa Bacon, BA, 1793 (Box 5)
  - Amasa Porter, BA, 1793 (Box 5)
  - Joseph Russell, BA, 1793 (Box 5)
  - John Sargeant, BA, 1793 (Box 5)
  - Joseph Washburn, BA, 1793 (Box 5)
  - Ezekiel Bacon, BA, 1794 (Box 5)
  - Josiah Stebbins, MA, 1794 (Box 5)
  - Stephen Twining, BA, 1795 (Box 5)
  - Amasa Porter, MA, 1796 (Box 5)
  - George Griffin, BA, 1797 (Box 5)
  - Benjamin Trumbull [honorary - S.T.D.?], 1797 (Box 5)
  - Jeremiah Day, MA, 1798 (Box 5)
  - Nathan Perkins, MA, 1798 (Box 5)
  - Stephen Twining, MA, 1798 (Box 5)
  - James Kingsley, BA, 1799 (Box 5)
  - Sidney Platt, BA (photocopy), 1799 (Box 5)
  - Truman Starr, BA, 1801 (Box 6)
  - Jeremiah Evarts, BA, 1802 (Box 6)
  - John Nelson Lloyd, BA, 1802 (Box 6)
  - Charles Shelton, BA, 1802 (Box 6)
  - Horace Holley, BA, 1803 (Box 6)
  - Pelatiah Perit, BA [photocopy], 1803 (Box 6)
  - Jacob Porter, BA, 1804 (Box 6)
  - Jacob Stedman, MA, 1804 (Box 6)
  - Charles Wetmore, BA, 1804 (Box 6)
  - Francis B. Winthrop, Jr., BA, 1804 (Box 6)
  - Charles Atwater, BA, 1805 (Box 6)
  - Edward Hooker, BA, 1805 (Box 6)
  - Mark Mead, MA, 1805 (Box 6)
  - D. Nathaniel Chauncey, BA, 1806 (Box 6)
  - Simeon Colton, BA, 1806 (Box 6)
  - Mills Day, MA, 1806 (Box 6)
  - Horace Holley, MA, 1806 (Box 6)
  - Jacob Porter, MA, 1806 (Box 6)
  - William Tulley, BA, 1806 (Box 6)
  - Leonard A. Daggett, BA, 1807 (Box 6)
  - Luther Hart, BA, 1807 (Box 6)
  - Ezra Kellogg, BA, 1807 (Box 6)
  - Isaac Osborn, BA, 1807 (Box 6)
  - Jonathan Cone, BA, 1808 (Box 6)
  - Charles Griswold, BA, 1808 (Box 6)
  - James Hillhouse, BA, 1808 (Box 6)
  - Edward Hooker, MA, 1808 (Box 6)
  - Samuel J. Hitchcock, BA, 1809 (Box 6)
  - Jonathan Lee, BA, 1809 (Box 6)
  - John S. W. Parkin, BA, 1809 (Box 6)
  - Hugh Robison, BA, 1809 (Box 6)
  - William Tully, MA, 1809 (Box 6)
  - Leonard Daggett, MA, 1810 (Box 6)
  - Araetius Bevil Hull, MA, 1810 (Box 6)
  - Jonathan Cone, MA, 1811 (Box 6)
  - Charles Griswold, MA, 1811 (Box 6)
  - James Hillsouse, MA, 1811 (Box 6)
  - Edwards Morse, BA, 1811 (Box 6)
  - Samuel Nichols, BA, 1811 (Box 6)
  - Julius Steele, BA, 1811 (Box 6)
  - Samuel J. Hitchcock, BA, 1811 (Box 6)
  - Richard C. Morse, BA, 1812 (Box 6)
  - [note - BA for 1812, Nathaniel Shaw Perkins, transferred to the Elias Perkins Papers, MSS 1013] (Box 6)
  - Sherman Converse, BA, 1813 (Box 6)
  - Milo Linus North, BA, 1813 (Box 6)
  - John Singletary, BA [no signatures, no seal], 1813 (Box 6)
  - Isaac Adriance, BA, 1814 (Box 6)
  - Lucius Leffingwell, BA, 1814 (Box 6)
  - Sidney Edwards Morse, MA, 1814 (Box 6)
  - Leonard Withington, BA, 1814 (Box 6)
  - [note - MA for N. S. Perins in Elias Perkins Papers, MSS 1013], 1815 (Box 6)
  - Isaac Bird, BA, 1816 (Box 6)
  - Ebenezer Andrews, BA, 1817 (Box 6)
  - Donald Chester, MA, 1817 (Box 6)
  - Jared Griswold, BA, 1817 (Box 6)
  - Jonathan Ingersoll, JD [honorary]
  - Hezekiah Sanford, MA, 1817 (Box 6)
  - Jonathan Edwards, BA, 1819 (Box 6)
  - Isaac Pound, MA, 1819 (Box 6)
  - Thomas Mather Smith, MA, 1819 (Box 6)
  - Augustus Alden, MA, 1820 (Box 7)
  - Abraham Baldwin, BA [original and 3 copies], 1820 (Box 7)
  - William De Lancey, MA, 1820 (Box 7)
  - Horatio Gridley, MA, 1820 (Box 7)
  - Jared Griswold, MA, 1820 (Box 7)
  - Loamni Ives Hoadley, MA, 1820 (Box 7)
  - Daniel H. Johnson, BA, 1820 (Box 7)
  - Jared Reid, MA, 1820 (Box 7)
  - Lewis Rodgers Starr, MA., 1820 (Box 7)
  - Samuel Wells, MA, 1820 (Box 7)
  - Timothy Dwight Woolsey, BA, 1820 (Box 7)
  - Robert Alden, BA, 1821 (Box 7)
  - Josiah Brewer, BA, 1821 (Box 7)
  - William Hodges, MA, 1821 (Box 7)
  - David Kimball, MA, 1821 (Box 7)
  - John Mitchell, BA, 1821 (Box 7)
  - Henry Porter, BA, 1821 (Box 7)
  - Alfred Terry, BA, 1821 (Box 7)
  - Leonard Withington, MA, 1821 (Box 7)
  - Edward Fort Barnes, BA, 1822 (Box 7)
  - Edward Fort Barnes BA, 1822 (Box 7)
  - Asa Butts, BA, 1822 (Box 7)
  - John Calhoun, LLD [honorary - 2 photocopies only], 1822 (Box 7)
  - Charles Hinsdale, MA, 1822 (Box 7)
  - William Law, BA, 1822 (Box 7)
  - Timothy Stillman, BA, 1822 (Box 7)
  - Ethan Andrews, MA, 1823 (Box 7)
  - Joseph Battel, MA [valid? - no signature - Battel listed as getting a BA honorary in 1823] (Box 7)
  - S. W. Brown, MD [original and copy], 1823 (Box 7)
  - Jared Foot, MA, 1823 (Box 7)
  - Increase Harrison, MD, 1823 (Box 7)
  - Richard Haughton, MA, 1823 (Box 7)
  - William Hubbard, MA, 1823 (Box 7)
  - David Mack, BA, 1823 (Box 7)
  - Seth Paddock, MA, 1823 (Box 7)
  - Samuel Perkins, MA, 1823 (Box 7)
  - Nathaniel Pratt, MA, 1823 (Box 7)
  - Judson Root, BA, 1823 (Box 7)
  - John Schroeder, MA, 1823 (Box 7)
  - John Sterling, MA, 1823 (Box 7)
  - William Sullivan, BA, 1823 (Box 7)
  - James Verplank, BA, 1823 (Box 7)
  - William Verplank, BA, 1823 (Box 7)
  - Theodore Woolsey, MA, 1824 (Box 7)
  - George Bigelow, MA, 1824 (Box 7)
  - Elias Brewer, BA, 1824 (Box 7)
  - Josiah Brewer, MA, 1824 (Box 7)
  - William Case, MA, 1824 (Box 7)
  - George Cowles, MA, 1824 (Box 7)
  - David Green, MA, 1824 (Box 7)
  - Theodore Hinsdale, MA, 1824 (Box 7)
  - Noah A. Lacy, MD [honorary? - no record of him], 1824 (Box 7)
  - Elias Warner Leavenworth, BA, 1824 (Box 7)
  - Erastus Maltby, MA, 1824 (Box 7)
  - John Mitchell, MA, 1824 (Box 7)
  - Isaac Peck, MA, 1824 (Box 7)
  - George William Perkins, BA, 1824 (Box 7)
  - Robert Gracie, MA, 1825 (Box 8)
  - Worthington Hooker, BA, 1825 (Box 8)
  - Lucius Leffingwell, MA, 1825 (Box 8)
  - William Rockwell, MA, 1825 (Box 8)
  - Edward Salisbury, MA, 1825 (Box 8)
  - John Bliss Watson, MA, 1825 (Box 8)
  - Edward Brewer, MA, 1826 (Box 8)
  - Samuel Hassard, BA, 1826 (Box 8)
  - David Mack, MA, 1826 (Box 8)
  - Asabel Phelps Mills, BA, 1826 (Box 8)
  - Dudley Phelps, MA, 1826 (Box 8)
  - Judson Root, MA, 1826 (Box 8)
  - David Smith, MA, 1826 (Box 8)
  - Thomas Smith, BA, 1826 (Box 8)
  - William Stevens, BA, 1826 (Box 8)
  - James Verplanck, MA, 1826 (Box 8)
  - Theron Baldwin, BA, 1827 (Box 8)
  - Charles R. Cooper, MD, 1827 (Box 8)
  - Joseph Cushing, BA, 1827 (Box 8)
  - Jeremiah Dennison, MA, 1827 (Box 8)
  - John M. Edwards, MA, 1827 (Box 8)
  - James Hunting [Huntting], MA, 1827 (Box 8)
  - Elias Leavenworth, MA, 1827 (Box 8)
  - Benjamin Silliman, MA, 1827 (Box 8)
  - William VanRensselaer, MA, 1827 (Box 8)
  - Elisha Smith Abernethy, MA, 1828 (Box 8)
  - Thomas Bond, MA, 1828 (Box 8)
  - John Butler, MA, 1828 (Box 8)
  - Joel Case, BA, 1828 (Box 8)
  - Abijah Catlin, MA, 1828 (Box 8)
  - Orson Cowles, BA, 1828 (Box 8)
  - Henry Noble Day, BA, 1828 (Box 8)
  - Worthington Hooker, MA, 1828 (Box 8)
  - Oliver Payson Hubbard, BA, 1828 (Box 8)
  - Joseph Nichols, BA, 1828 (Box 8)
  - Darius Mead, BA, 1828 (Box 8)
  - George Perkins, BA, 1828 (Box 8)
  - Amos Blanchard, MA, 1829 (Box 8)
  - James D. Chapman, MA, 1829 (Box 8)
  - Sherman Day, MA, 1829 (Box 8)
  - William Dwight, MA, 1829 (Box 8)
  - Nathaniel Perkins, MD [incomplete signatures], 1829 (Box 8)
  - Julius Rockwell, MA, 1829 (Box 8)
  - David Seymour, MA, 1829 (Box 8)
  - Stephen Thatcher, MA, 1829 (Box 8)
  - Henry Bernard [Barnard?], BA, 1830 (Box 9)
  - Joshua Trowbridge Eaton, BA, 1830 (Box 9)
  - Mason Grosvenor, MA, 1830 (Box 9)
  - William Lester, MA, 1830 (Box 9)
  - Anson Little, MA, 1830 (Box 9)
  - John McPhail, MA, 1830 (Box 9)
  - John Rogers Murray, BA, 1830 (Box 9)
  - Elijah Train, MA, 1830 (Box 9)
  - David Bacon, BA, 1831 (Box 9)
  - Otis Baker, BA, 1831 (Box 9)
  - Theron Baldwin, MA, 1831 (Box 9)
  - David Bliss, BA, 1831 (Box 9)
  - Orson Cowles, MA, 1831 (Box 9)
  - Henry N. Day, MA, 1831 (Box 9)
  - Ezra Fairchild, MA, 1831 (Box 9)
  - William Hopkins, MA, 1831 (Box 9)
  - Oliver Hubbard, MA, 1831 (Box 9)
  - William Oaks, MA, 1831 (Box 9)
  - John Palmer, MA, 1831 (Box 9)
  - Noah Porter, BA, 1831 (Box 9)
  - Thomas Seddon, BA, 1831 (Box 9)
  - Alexander Sessions, BA, 1832 (Box 9)
  - Calvin Colton, MA, 1832 (Box 9)
  - John Colton, BA, 1832 (Box 9)
  - Asa Drury, MA, 1832 (Box 9)
  - Thomas Evans, BA, 1832 (Box 9)
  - Henry Gleason, MA, 1832 (Box 9)
  - Thomas Hubbard, MA, 1832 (Box 9)
  - George Kingsley, BA, 1832 (Box 9)
  - Stephen Atwater Potwine, BA, 1832 (Box 9)
  - Edward Salisbury, BA, 1832 (Box 9)
  - Corydon Sperry, BA, 1832 (Box 9)
  - George Tenney, MA, 1832 (Box 9)
  - Epaphroditus C. Bacon, BA, 1833 (Box 9)
  - William H. Beecher, MA [honorary]
  - James Dwight Dana, BA, 1833 (Box 9)
  - Eleazar B. Downing, MD [honorary], 1833 (Box 9)
  - Edward Jones, MA, 1833 (Box 9)
  - John R. Murray, MA, 1833 (Box 9)
  - Benjamin Neill, MA, 1833 (Box 9)
  - William Tallman, MA, 1833 (Box 9)
  - Joseph Tyler, MA, 1833 (Box 9)
  - Robert Birch, MA, 1834 (Box 9)
  - Erastus Cole, MA [honorary], 1834 (Box 9)
  - Daniel Hall, BA, 1834 (Box 9)
  - Junius Hall, MA, 1834 (Box 9)
  - James Matheson, STD, 1834 (Box 9)
  - Milo North, MD, 1834 (Box 9)
  - Luzerne Rae, MA, 1834 (Box 9)
  - Nathan Seymour, BA, 1834 (Box 9)
  - Joshua Spencer, MA [honorary], 1834 (Box 9)
  - Charles Taylor, BA, 1834 (Box 9)
  - John Colton, MA (Box 10)
  - Edward Dunning, MA, 1835 (Box 10)
  - Henry Eddy, MA, 1835 (Box 10)
  - George Kingsley, MA, 1835 (Box 10)
  - Lorenzo Langstroth, MA, 1835 (Box 10)
  - Horatio Nelson, MA, 1835 (Box 10)
  - George Nichols, BA, 1835 (Box 10)
  - William Noble, MA, 1835 (Box 10)
  - Corydon Sperry, MA, 1835 (Box 10)
  - John Wallis, MA, 1835 (Box 10)
  - Epaphroditus Bacon, MA, 1836 (Box 10)
  - Elishiama Brandgee, MA, 1836 (Box 10)
  - Horatio Day, MA, 1836 (Box 10)
  - Hiram Doane, MA, 1836 (Box 10)
  - Julian Vail Pettis, BA, 1836 (Box 10)
  - Oliver Bidwell, MA, 1837 (Box 10)
  - Thomas Bradstreet, MA, 1837 (Box 10)
  - Job Swift Gold, MA, 1837 (Box 10)
  - Chauncey Goodrich, BA, 1837 (Box 10)
  - John Lounsbury, MD, 1837 (Box 10)
  - William Bartlett Morse, BA, 1837 (Box 10)
  - Samuel St. John, MA, 1837 (Box 10)
  - William Selfridge, BA, 1837 (Box 10)
  - Nathan Seymour, MA, 1837 (Box 10)
  - Joseph Spencer, BA, 1837 (Box 10)
  - Charles Woodward Stearns, BA, 1837 (Box 10)
  - Dorson Sykes, MA, 1837 (Box 10)
  - William Taylor, MA, 1837 (Box 10)
  - Francis Bacon, BA, 1838 (Box 10)
  - Samuel Davis, MA, 1838 (Box 10)
  - Albert Dodd, BA, 1838 (Box 10)
  - Edward Dwight, MA, 1838 (Box 10)
  - William Law, BA, 1838 (Box 10)
  - George Nichols, MA, 1838 (Box 10)
  - James Nooney, MA, 1838 (Box 10)
  - Edward Smith, MA, 1838 (Box 10)
  - William Wright, MA, 1838 (Box 10)
  - John Beach, BA, 1839 (Box 10)
  - Horatio Bryant, MD, 1839 (Box 10)
  - Edward Cowles, MA, 1839 (Box 10)
  - Dan Curtiss, MA, 1839 (Box 10)
  - David Daggett, BA, 1839 (Box 10)
  - Horatio Day, MA, 1839 (Box 10)
  - Eugene Edwards, BA, 1839 (Box 10)
  - Samuel Fowler, BA, 1839 (Box 10)
  - Thomas Jacocks, BA, 1839 (Box 10)
  - Charles Morse, BA, 1839 (Box 10)
  - Julian Vailpettis, MA, 1839 (Box 10)
  - Charles Prindle, MA, 1839 (Box 10)
  - Charles Turner Torrey, MA, 1839 (Box 10)
  - William Wahington, MA, 1839 (Box 10)
  - Dillon Williams, MA, 1839 (Box 10)
  - William Perkins Williams, BA, 1839 (Box 10)
  - Benjamin Catlin, MD, 1840 (Box 11)
  - George Colton, BA, 1840 (Box 11)
  - William Evarts, MA, 1840 (Box 11)
  - Chauncey Goodrich, MA, 1840 (Box 11)
  - Orlo Daniel Hine, MA, 1840 (Box 11)
  - James Mason Hoppin, BA, 1840 (Box 11)
  - Nelson Smith, BA, 1840 (Box 11)
  - Francis Bacon, MA, 1841 (Box 11)
  - Louis DeOnis Champlin, BA, 1841 (Box 11)
  - Lot Curran Clark, MA, 1841 (Box 11)
  - Flavel Athington Dickinson, BA, 1841 (Box 11)
  - James Ferguson, MA, 1841 (Box 11)
  - Ezra Hall Gillet, BA, 1841 (Box 11)
  - Charles Sherman Minor, BA, 1841 (Box 11)
  - Donald Grant Mitchell, BA, 1841 (Box 11)
  - James Nooney, MA, 1841 (Box 11)
  - Lemuel Parsons, MA, 1841 (Box 11)
  - Ebenezer Spalding, MA, 1841 (Box 11)
  - Thomas Talcott, MA, 1841 (Box 11)
  - Daniel Brooks, MA, 1842 (Box 11)
  - Zalmon Burr, MA, 1842 (Box 11)
  - Francis Cornwell, BA, 1842 (Box 11)
  - Henry Plumer Keyes, BA, 1842 (Box 11)
  - Augustus MacDonough, MA, 1842 (Box 11)
  - John Jay Orton, BA, 1842 (Box 11)
  - Horatio Peck, MA, 1842 (Box 11)
  - Nathaniel Shaw Perkins, BA, 1842 (Box 11)
  - Leander Elmer Wakefield, BA, 1842 (Box 11)
  - Robert William Wright, BA, 1842 (Box 11)
  - George Blagden, MA, 1843 (Box 11)
  - David Louis Daggett, MD, 1843 (Box 11)
  - Joseph Grout, MA, 1843 (Box 11)
  - James Jessup, MA, 1843 (Box 11)
  - William Lathrop Kingsley, BA, 1843 (Box 11)
  - George Clark Lucas, BA, 1843 (Box 11)
  - Cale Pelton, MA, 1843 (Box 11)
  - Joseph Smith, MA, 1843 (Box 11)
  - Levi Abbott, MA, 1844 (Box 11)
  - James Babcock, MA, 1844 (Box 11)
  - William Bird, BA [honorary], 1844 (Box 11)
  - Lucien Birdseye, MA, 1844 (Box 11)
  - William Dwight, MA, 1844 (Box 11)
  - Augustus Gillet, MA, 1844 (Box 11)
  - Ezra Gillet, MA, 1844 (Box 11)
  - John Hamlen, MA, 1844 (Box 11)
  - William Johnstone, MA, 1844 (Box 11)
  - Joel Newton, MA, 1844 (Box 11)
  - Effingham Nichols, MA, 1844 (Box 11)
  - Ebenezer Rogers, MA, 1844 (Box 11)
  - James Wadsworth, MA, 1844 (Box 11)
  - William Andrews, MA, 1845 (Box 11)
  - James Baldwin, MA, 1845 (Box 11)
  - Philander Button, MA, 1845 (Box 11)
  - Elisha Cook, MA, 1845 (Box 11)
  - William Downs, BA, 1845 (Box 11)
  - Burdett Hart, MA, 1845 (Box 11)
  - Daniel Henshaw, MA, 1845 (Box 11)
  - Albert Mathews, MA, 1845 (Box 11)
  - James Munroe, BA, 1845 (Box 11)
  - John Jay Orton, MA, 1845 (Box 11)
  - John Pinkerton, MA, 1845 (Box 11)
  - Isaac St. John, BA, 1845 (Box 11)
  - Alexander Sessions, MA, 1845 (Box 11)
  - David Sherman, MA., 1845 (Box 11)
  - James Silkman, BA, 1845 (Box 11)
  - Ira Smith, MA, 1845 (Box 11)
  - William Stokes, MA, 1845 (Box 11)
  - Charles Wells, BA, 1845 (Box 11)
  - Robert Aikman, MA, 1846 (Box 11)
  - Samuel Andrews, MA, 1846 (Box 11)
  - Albert Barnes, BA, 1846 (Box 11)
  - Edward Cowles, MA, 1846 (Box 11)
  - James Dill, MA, 1846 (Box 11)
  - Mills Gelston, MA, 1846 (Box 11)
  - Josiah King, MA, 1846 (Box 11)
  - William Kingeley, MA, 1846 (Box 11)
  - John Lambert, BA, 1846 (Box 11)
  - George Newton, MA, 1846 (Box 11)
  - William Peck, MA, 1846 (Box 11)
  - Burritt Smith, MA, 1846 (Box 11)
  - Robert Stanton, MA, 1846 (Box 11)
  - Henry Thornton Steele, BA, 1846 (Box 11)
  - John Weekes, MA, 1846 (Box 11)
  - William Downs, BA, 1847 (Box 11)
  - Louis Dudley, BA, 1847 (Box 11)
  - William Hawe, BA, 1847 (Box 11)
  - John Munn, BA, 1847 (Box 11)
  - Francis Palmer, MA, 1847 (Box 11)
  - James Alexander Ruthven, BA, 1847 (Box 11)
  - John Wesley Shepherd, MA, 1847 (Box 11)
  - William Minor Williams, MA, 1847 (Box 11)
  - Henry Trowbridge Wiswall, BA, 1847 (Box 11)
  - William Lathrop Bliss, MA, 1848 (Box 11)
  - Charles Astor Bristed, MA, 1848 (Box 11)
  - Marshall Mason Fitch, BA, 1848 (Box 11)
  - James Griswold, BA, 1848 (Box 11)
  - George Langdon, BA, 1848 (Box 11)
  - Arthur Dimon Osborne, BA, 1848 (Box 11)
  - Isaac Munroe St. John, MA, 1848 (Box 11)
  - Theodore Winthrop, BA, 1848 (Box 11)
  - Sanders Diefendorf, MA, 1848 (Box 11)
  - Franklin Woodbury Fisk, BA, 1849 (Box 11)
  - Charles Josiah Pennington, MA, 1849 (Box 11)
  - Henry Thornton Steele, MA, 1849 (Box 11)
  - Charles Jones, MA, 1850 (Box 12)
  - Joseph Bardwell Lyman, BA, 1850 (Box 12)
  - John Harbeck Meeker, MA, 1850 (Box 12)
  - Hubert Anson Newton, BA, 1850 (Box 12)
  - Thomas Young Simons, MA, 1850 (Box 12)
  - Joseph Perkins Griswold, BA, 1850 (Box 12)
  - George Washington Lyon, BA, 1851 (Box 12)
  - Bennett Warner Morse, BA, 1851 (Box 12)
  - Theodore Thornton Munger, BA, 1851 (Box 12)
  - Theodore Winthrop, MA, 1851 (Box 12)
  - Henry Clay Blakeslee, BA, 1852 (Box 12)
  - Fisk Parsons Brewer, BA, 1852 (Box 12)
  - William Henry Brewer, BA, 1852 (Box 12)
  - Franklin Woodbury Fisk, MA, 1852 (Box 12)
  - Horatio Hollister, MA, 1852 (Box 12)
  - William Augustus Reynolds, BA, 1852 (Box 12)
  - William Baldwin Ross, BA, 1852 (Box 12)
  - George Blagden Safford, BA, 1852 (Box 12)
  - John Isaac Ira Adams, MA, 1853 (Box 12)
  - William Pope Aikin, BA, 1853 (Box 12)
  - Samuel Watson Brown, MA, 1853 (Box 12)
  - Moses Culver, MA, 1853 (Box 12)
  - Andrew Cheves Dulles, BA, 1853 (Box 12)
  - James Raymond Goodrich, BA, 1853 (Box 12)
  - Hubert Anson Newton, MA, 1853 (Box 12)
  - Samuel Brigham Spooner, BA, 1853 (Box 12)
  - John Worthington Hooker, BA, 1854 (Box 12)
  - Henry E. Howland, BA, 1854 (Box 12)
  - George Washington Lyon, MA, 1854 (Box 12)
  - William Pitt Riddell, MA, 1854 (Box 12)
  - George Blagden Safford, MA, 1854 (Box 12)
  - Henry Clay Blakeslee, MA, 1855 (Box 12)
  - Fisk Parsons Brewer, MA, 1855 (Box 12)
  - James Eaton, MA, 1855 (Box 12)
  - Jonathan Goodhue, MA, 1855 (Box 12)
  - William Augustus Reynolds, MA, 1855 (Box 12)
  - William Baldwin Ross, MA, 1855 (Box 12)
  - Charles Tyler, BA, 1855 (Box 12)
  - William Wheeler, BA, 1855 (Box 12)
  - Daniel Willes, MA, 1855 (Box 12)
  - William Pope Aikin, MA, 1856 (Box 12)
  - William Bird, MA, 1856 (Box 12)